[{"question": " ohh. mmm.", "answer": "", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hey, you have got to try this cheesecake.", "answer": " oh, y\u0092know i'm not that much of a sweet tooth. i\u0097\u0097wow. my god, so creamy. oh my god, this is the best cheesecake i have ever had. where did you get this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  it was at the front door. when i got home. somebody sent it to us.", "answer": " chandler, this is not addressed to you. this is addressed to mrs. braverman downstairs.  thief.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " i\u0097no! i didn't read the box before i opened it. and you can't return a box after you've opened the box.", "answer": " why, why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " because it's too delicious.", "answer": " chandler, you stole this cheesecake. that is wrong.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " no-no-no! it is going to be okay, because mrs. braverman is gonna send away for a free one and that way we all win! the only losers are the big cheesecake conglomerate,  momma\u0092s little bakery.  i feel terrible, i\u0092m a horrible, horrible, horrible person.", "answer": "  oh, i\u0092m sorry what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " all right, i should get going, big day a work. y\u0092know i\u0092m in a coma? today, they do this test on me and it turns out i\u0092m not brain dead.", "answer": " so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " ah-ah-ah mr. smartie pants, it\u0092s just not my character that\u0092s not brain dead. hey, so pheebs, we still on for tonight?", "answer": " absolutely!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " i\u0092ll see you at 8:00.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " oh, what\u0092s at 8:00?", "answer": " oh, i have dinner plans with joey. we get together about once a month to discuss the rest of you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " wow, did not know that! may i say how lovely you look today?", "answer": " duly noted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " thanks.   oh! so for tomorrow, do you want to rent a car and drive down together or what?", "answer": " what are you talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " cousin frannie\u0092s wedding, its tomorrow night.", "answer": " you were invited?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " my god, i can\u0092t believe this! i mean i knew that mom and dad were invited, but i thought that was it! i mean from the ages 7 to 9 frannie and i were inseparable!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " well, maybe since the age of 9, frannie\u0092s made some new friends.", "answer": " well l-look okay, it\u0092s probably just a mistake. let me call aunt sheryl okay? maybe you are invited and the invitation just got lost in the mail.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " yeah, well you call her and tell her that y\u0092know when we were kids her precious little frannie tried to undress me several times, okay? and if i hadn\u0092t have stopped her, there probably wouldn\u0092t even be a wedding to go too.", "answer": " y\u0092know, she tried to undress me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " joseph francis tribbiani are you home yet?!!", "answer": " umm, i think he\u0092s still out. what\u0092s wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  \"pheebs, can\u0092t make it, got a date. talk to you later. big daddy.\"  big daddy?", "answer": " oh that\u0092s a nickname we were trying out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " oh! here\u0092s joseph francis!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh-wha-ho! what are you middle naming me for?! i left you a note!", "answer": " so what?! that doesn\u0092t give you the right to ditch me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " hey, you can cancel plans with friends if there is the possibility for sex!", "answer": " phoebe he\u0092s right, that is the rule.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i don\u0092t accept this rule. when me make plans, i expect you to show up. okay, i can\u0092t just be a way to kill time \u0091til you meet someone better! y\u0092know boyfriends and girlfriends come and go, but this  is for life!", "answer": " wow! i\u0092m so sorry; i had no idea it would bother you this much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " well, it does.", "answer": " okay, can i-can i make it up to you? huh? i\u0092m sorry.  how about uh, dinner tomorrow night?! i\u0092ll pay for myself!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " okay, you wore me down.", "answer": " hey joe, while you\u0092re over there how about another beer for the ross-a-tron?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " another cheesecake came! they delivered it to the wrong address again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " so just bring it back downstairs, what\u0092s the problem?", "answer": " i can\u0092t seem to say goodbye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " are you serious?! chandler, we ate an entire cheesecake two days ago and you want more?", "answer": " well i\u0092ve forgotten what it tastes like okay?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " it was cheesecake. it was fine. it had a buttery, crumbly, graham cracker crust, with a very rich yet light, cream cheese filling\u009a  wow! my whole mouth just filled with saliva!", "answer": "  y\u0092know what? forget it! we are just hungry! we have not had lunch! we are just light-headed! so let us go out and have lunch and forget about the cheesecake.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah and we\u0092ll drop it off downstairs so that we\u0092re not tempted.", "answer": " good idea. where do you want to go to lunch?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " awww! mel torme died.", "answer": " joey, that paper\u0092s like a year old!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " aw! does that mean the sam goody\u0092s sale is over?!", "answer": "  hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " so i finally heard back from aunt sheryl and apparently it wasn\u0092t a mistake. ahh, there\u0092s-there\u0092s limited seating in the hall.", "answer": " limited seating?!  i am just one tiny person!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " well yeah, but she doesn\u0092t know that. i mean, the last time she saw you-you would\u0092ve turned one of those little wedding chairs into kindling.", "answer": "  limited seating! oh, that is such a lame excuse! that\u0092s not the reason she\u0092s not inviting me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh what\u0092s the big deal?! i wasn\u0092t even invited to the ceremony, just the reception. and-and y\u0092know what? if it makes you feel any better, joan and i will just make an appearance and then, and then we\u0092ll-we\u0092ll leave early as a sign of protest.", "answer": " joan?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yeah, joan tedeski my date. she\u0092s an assistant professor in the linguistics department. tall, very beautiful, and despite what some people say, not broad backed!", "answer": " wait a minute, you got ross gellar and guest?! i wasn\u0092t invited and you got \"and guest?!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " uh-uh, excuse me, i do have to interrupt on ross\u0092s behalf. i-i think the rule applies here y\u0092know, since she has a chance to get on broad back\u009a", "answer": "  not broad backed!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " wait a minute, y\u0092know, you\u0092re bringing me!", "answer": " what? i can\u0092t cancel on joan!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " why not?!", "answer": " bec\u0097did you not hear me?! she\u0092s an assistant professor in the linguistics department, okay? they\u0092re wild! why do you want to come anyway?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " because! she\u0092s my cousin. i mean, we grew up together! we\u0092re family y\u0092know? well that\u0092s important to me.", "answer": " okay, all right, i\u0092ll take you. i\u0092ll go call joan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " aww that\u0092s nice. family should be there, huh? this is her wedding, happiest day of her life.", "answer": "  we\u0092ll see.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " well, thank you for lunch.", "answer": " what? wait a minute, i didn\u0092t pay, i thought you paid!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " so apparently we just don\u0092t pay for food anymore.  do you see what i see?", "answer": "  its still there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " she could be out of town. maybe she\u0092ll be gone for months.", "answer": " by then, the cheesecake may have gone bad. we don\u0092t want her to come back to bad cheesecake.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " no that could kill her.", "answer": " well, we don\u0092t want that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " no so we\u0092re protecting her.", "answer": " but we should take it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " but we should move quick.", "answer": " why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " because i think i just heard her moving around in there.", "answer": " go! go! go! go! go! go! go! go! go! go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": "   oh my god! that\u0092s david!", "answer": " david who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " david the scientist guy, david that i was in love with, david who went to russia and broke my heart david!", "answer": "  oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " oh, you say someone\u0092s name enough, they turn around.", "answer": " phoebe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " david!  what-what are you doing here? aren\u0092t you supposed to be in russia?", "answer": " yeah, i\u0092m just, i\u0092m just in town for a conference. umm, god you look phenomenal!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " well\u009a yeah. you look great too. did you get a haircut?", "answer": " yeah. well i-i got like thirty of them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " umm, look i-i-i got a confession to make\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " uh, i-i-i was hoping to run into you here. i didn\u0092t know whether i should call or not, y\u0092know i-i was only in town for a few days. and y\u0092know, i didn\u0092t want to intrude on your life or-or anything like that, but i-i really wanted to see you and\u0097but i didn\u0092t know if you wanted to see me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " well, of course i would want to see you. i\u009ai think about you all the time.", "answer": " really? because i think about you all the time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " i mean, there\u0092s a statue in minsk\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " that reminds me of you so much, i mean umm, it-it\u0092s actually of lenin. but, y\u0092know at certain angles\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " umm, anyway\u009ado you want to have dinner tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  yes! oh no!", "answer": "  oh. uh, what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " i can\u0092t. i can\u0092t believe i have plans, i can\u0092t. can you do it tomorrow night though?", "answer": " uh no, i have to go in a few hours. i have to be on the red-eye. well listen, y\u0092know, next time you\u0092re in minsk umm\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " phoebe, can i talk to you for a second?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " well, i have plans with joey tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " so! he\u0092ll understand!", "answer": " no he won\u0092t. and that\u0092s not even the point! monica, i made a whole speech about you do not cancel plans with friends! and now y\u0092know what? just because, potentially, the love of my life comes back from russia just for one night, i-i should change my beliefs?! i should change beliefs! no! no! no, if i don\u0092t have my principles, i don\u0092t have anything!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " god, you are so strong.", "answer": " or! i should rush through dinner with joey and i can meet david at 9:00! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  oh my god! that is so good!", "answer": " i\u0092m full, and yet i know if i stop eating this, i\u0092ll regret", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  what do you got there?", "answer": " oh it\u0092s umm, it\u0092s tofu cake. do you want some?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " what are you doing tonight?", "answer": " huh? uh\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh!  sorry. uh, i\u0092ve got those plans with phoebe, why?", "answer": " oh really? uh, monica said she had a date at 9:00.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " what?! tonight?!", "answer": " that\u0092s what monica said.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh here, i think this is us.  yeah.", "answer": " limited seating my ass. let\u0092s see who made the cut.  hi! the wedding guest: hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " i\u0092m monica gellar. who do you know the bride and groom? the wedding guest: oh, i used to work with frannie.", "answer": " used to work with her. used to! i\u0092m a relative and i didn\u0092t get invited! a blood relative! blood!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  stop saying, \"blood\" to strangers.", "answer": "  so, how about you huh? how do you know the happy couple? the second guest: we went to college with both of them and now we live next door.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " are you guys ready?", "answer": " yes! i will have the green salad, umm the house salad, and water\u0092s fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  and for you sir?", "answer": " yeah, this slow roasted salmon, just how slow are we talkin\u0092 here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " it\u0092s uh, it\u0092s already been roasted.", "answer": " ohh, then no. maybe i should hear those specials again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " oh well, that changes everything!  y\u0092know what pheebs?", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " you were right before. i mean, friends are so important.", "answer": "  yeah, i\u0092m very wise. i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " y\u0092know-y\u0092know what i really want?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " is to have a long, long talk. y\u0092know? get joey out on the open road and really open him up.", "answer": "  any progress?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yes! i will have the lobster ravioli.", "answer": " god joey, this is taking forever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " what\u0092s the rush? what?", "answer": " w-w\u0097i just\u0097it\u0092s that\u0097i have\u0097y\u0092know i have-i have an appointment. and it\u0092s very important.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " whoa-whoa, what is it?", "answer": " well\u009a it\u0092s a date.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " a date?! no, no pheebs you-you must be mistaken, because i know you wouldn\u0092t schedule a date on the same night you have plans with a friend!", "answer": " come on joey, don\u0092t make me feel badly about this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no, i\u0092m gonna!! that\u0092s right! yeah, you made me feel really guilty about goin\u0092 out with that girl! like-like-like i did something terrible to you! and now pheebs, you\u0092re doing the same thing!", "answer": " that\u0097it\u0092s not the same thing! this is totally different! this is with david! remember david, the scientist guy? okay, he\u0092s very special to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " okay, well my girl from the other night was special. she was a scientist too!", "answer": " she was?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " well, she graduated from high school!", "answer": " okay, whatever. y\u0092know what? i don\u0092t have time have time to convince you because he\u0092s only here for four hours, and i\u0092m gonna go see him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " fine!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " fine!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey! oh, i was just about to leave. i-i-i-i didn\u0092t think you were coming.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh, i wouldn\u0092t miss this.", "answer": " well, i\u0092m very glad you\u0092re here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " are you eating the cheesecake without me?!", "answer": "  mm-mmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " i will give you a hundred dollars to whistle right now.  how can you eat the cheesecake without me?!", "answer": " oh, what are you going to do?! are you gonna go run tell monica?! are you gonna tell joey?! no! because then you will have to tell them what we did! we are desert stealers! we are living outside the law!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " what?! what?!", "answer": " oh yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " wait a minute!", "answer": " oh yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " oh yes! oh yes!", "answer": " you think i trust you with it?! no! we\u0092re gonna split it! you take half and i take half!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " well that\u0092s not fair, you\u0092ve already had some!", "answer": " what? oh, well then y\u0092know what? i think monica would be very interested to know that you called her cheesecake dry and mealy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " what do we use to split it?", "answer": " okay!  all right, pick a half.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": "  okay well, this side looks bigger. uh\u009a there\u0092s more crust on this side. y\u0092know? so, maybe if i measured\u009a", "answer": " oh for god sake just pick a piece!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " that\u0092s also the smaller piece.  okay, there you go. enjoy your half my friend, but that is it. no sharing. no switching, and don\u0092t come crying to me if you eat your piece to fast.  oh!!!!", "answer": "  ohhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " okay, you gotta give me some of your piece.", "answer": " oh-ho-ho-ho-no! no! no switching! no sharing, and don\u0092t come crying to me! ha-ha-ha! i may just sit here and have my cake all day! just sit here in the hallway and eat my\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " ross, sweetheart!", "answer": " oh, hey aunt millie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " isn\u0092t it a beautiful wedding?!", "answer": " yes, yes it is. it\u0092s uh\u009a  every time on the lips! why?! why on lips?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " now wait a minute, you be nice! all right? i didn\u0092t bring you here so you can ambush her.", "answer": " frannie was the one who found your playboys and showed them to mom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  monica! what\u009a", "answer": " am i doing here? why? surprised to see me? ross brought me. how do you like that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": "  hi frannie, congratulations.", "answer": " you invite my brother, you invite my whole family, and not me?! why?! what\u0097why wouldn\u0092t you want me at your wedding? what could i have possibly done?!  stuart!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " oh, i hate this but i-i-i have to go. i-i can\u0092t miss my flight.", "answer": " are you sure? i\u0092ll bet there\u0092s another flight to minsk in like\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " that\u0092s really beautiful. what does it mean?", "answer": " please, clean my beakers. i don\u0092t get out of the lab much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " that\u0092s good. i got to admit, i thought it was something else.", "answer": " yeah, i\u009a well i really actually wanted to say umm, that, but um, i figured i probably shouldn\u0092t because y\u0092know, i\u009ahave to leave.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " you\u0092re right! you\u0092re right. don\u0092t say it.", "answer": " i-i do though.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": "  okay, now\u0092s not the time joey. all right? you can yell at me tomorrow.", "answer": " no! no! no pheebs, i\u0092m not gonna yell at you. i just y\u0092know, started thinking about you and david and i\u009aremember how bummed you were the first time he left. and i just\u009a oh pheebs, come here.  are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " hey, y\u0092know you could always visit him.", "answer": " oh right, like they\u0092re gonna let me have a passport.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " anything i can do? whatever you need.", "answer": " well\u0097but\u0097now, if-if you can achieve positronic distillation of sub-atomic particles y\u0092know before he does, then he can come back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " oh! yay! look! there\u0092s a piece that doesn\u0092t have floor on", "answer": " stick to your side!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " oh wait i forgot my wrap.", "answer": " what? oh, okay. wait here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " hi sweetie! are you leaving?", "answer": " well\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}]